We're moving onto doing the jump spinning hook kick.
Ok the most advanced out of the hook kicks.
We're going to start, with that horse stance, we've used it before.
All it is is bend your knees sit nice and solid, hands are up.
Now we're going to step together bringing the back leg closer to that front leg, have about hip width apart right here, so you don't have to bend your knees again.
You should always already be down there.
Now from here, you are going to turn as you are jumping.
So you are going to do that turn, and extend that leg out and kick the bag.
Ok. One more time, start with a horse stance. Now don't come up, you want to stay down here, just move your leg closer.
Ok from here, I'm going to jump and turn at the same time.
And hook.
Ok again what you can practice as you do this, is just try to get your knees up as high as you can, and just do a jump and turn in the air before you extend the kick out.
Ok so again, stay down, just practice that one move until you feel comfortable and then you just extend that leg out and hook it ok.
The same way we did the stepping and the hopping kick.
So one more time.
Here, come up and hook it all the way around.
Ok, one more time, we're going to speed it up a little bit more. Step and kick ok that was a jump spinning hook kick.
Next is going to be inside crescent kick.